<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Legio Mariae</string>

    <string name="opcao_eventos">Events</string>
    <string name="opcao_terco">Rosary</string>
    <string name="opcao_oracoes">Tessera</string>
    <string name="opcao_trabalhos">Works</string>
    <string name="opcao_ordemReuniao">Meeting</string>
    <string name="opcao_oracaoFrank">Prayer for Frank Duff</string>
    <string name="opcao_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="activity_novo_evento">New Event</string>
    <string name="salvar">Save</string>
    <string name="cancelar">Cancel</string>

    <string name="nome_evento">Name of the Event</string>
    <string name="hint_nome_evento">Type the name</string>
    <string name="local_evento">Location</string>
    <string name="hint_local_evento">Type the name of the location</string>
    <string name="horario_evento">Time</string>
    <string name="hint_horario_evento">Click here to set the time</string>
    <string name="data_evento">Date</string>
    <string name="hint_data_evento">Click here to set the date</string>

    <string name="dialogNome">Name</string>
    <string name="hintDialogNome">Ex. Evangelization</string>
    <string name="dialogQtade">Quantity</string>
    <string name="hintDialogQtade">Ex. 1</string>
    <string name="dialogTitulo">New Work</string>
    <string name="dialogExecption">Ops, a field was not filled</string>

    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="mensagem_lixo_evento">\tTo insert a new event click on the pencil.\n
        \tTo delte the event drag the event to the left or right</string>
    <string name="mensagem_lixo_trabalho">\tTo insert a new work click on the pencil.\n
        \tTo delte the event drag the work to the left or right</string>

    <string name="key_nome_perfil">nome</string>
    <string name="key_nome_presidium">presidium</string>
    <string name="key_foto_perfil">foto</string>
    <string name="key_foto_modificada">modificou</string>

    <string name="foto_perfil">Profile Photo</string>
    <string name="nome_usuario">Name of the User</string>
    <string name="nome_setting_dialog">Type your name</string>
    <string name="nome_praesidium">Name of the Praesidium</string>
    <string name="nome_paesidium_settings_dialog">Type the name of your praesidium</string>


    <string name="default_nome_perfil">Set your name and of your praesidium</string>
    <string name="default_nome_presidium">on Settings</string>
    <string name="default_summary_foto">Set yout profile picture</string>

    <string name="content_description">Profile Picture</string>

    <string-array name="tercos">
        <item>Joyful</item>
        <item>Glorious</item>
        <item>Luminous</item>
        <item>Sorroyful</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="oracoes">
        <item>Opening</item>
        <item>Catena</item>
        <item>Concluding</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="eventos">Eventos</string>

    <string-array name="Gozoso">
        <item>Monday and Saturday</item>
        <item>1st Mystery: The Annunciation of the Lord to Mary</item>
        <item>2nd Mystery: The Visitation of Mary to Elizabeth</item>
        <item>3rd Mystery: The Nativity of our Lord Jesus Christ</item>
        <item>4th Mystery: The Presentation of our Lord</item>
        <item>5th Mystery: Finding Jesus in the Temple at age 12</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Luminoso">
        <item>Thursday</item>
        <item>1st Mystery: The Baptism in the Jordan</item>
        <item>2nd Mystery: The Wedding at Cana</item>
        <item>3rd Mystery: The Proclamation of the Kingdom</item>
        <item>4th Mystery: The Transfiguration</item>
        <item>5th Mystery: The Institution of the Eucharist</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Doloroso">
        <item>Tuesday and Friday</item>
        <item>1st Mystery: The Agony of Jesus in the Garden</item>
        <item>2nd Mystery: The Scourging at the Pillar</item>
        <item>3rd Mystery: Jesus is Crowned with Thorns</item>
        <item>4th Mystery: Jesus Carried the Cross</item>
        <item>5th Mystery: The Crucifixion of our Lord</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Glorioso">
        <item>Wednesday and Sunday</item>
        <item>1st Mystery: The Resurrection of Jesus Christ</item>
        <item>2nd Mystery: The Ascension of Jesus to Heaven</item>
        <item>3rd Mystery: The Descent of the Holy Ghost</item>
        <item>4th Mystery: The Assumption of Mary into Heaven</item>
        <item>5th Mystery: Mary is Crowned as Queen of Heaven and Earth</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="oracoes_iniciais">
        In the name of the Father, etc.\n
        Come, O Holy Spirit, fill the hearts of your faithful, and
        enkindle in them the fire of your love.\n\n
        V/. Send forth your Spirit, and they shall be created.\n
        R/. And you shall renew the face of the earth.\n\n

        Let us pray\n\n
        God our Father, pour out the gifts of your Holy Spirit on
        the world. You sent the Spirit on your Church to begin the
        teaching of the gospel: now let the Spirit continue to work in
        the world through the hearts of all who believe. Through
        Christ our Lord. Amen.\n\n
        V/. You, O Lord, will open my lips.\n
        R/. And my tongue shall announce your praise.\n\n
        V/. Incline unto my aid, O God.\n
        R/. O Lord, make haste to help me.\n\n
        V/. Glory be to the Father, etc.\n
        R/. As it was in the beginning, etc.\n\n

        (Then follow five decades of the rosary with the Hail, Holy Queen!)\n\n

        V/. Pray for us, O holy Mother of God.\n
        R/. That we may be made worthy of the promises of Christ.
        Let us pray\n\n
        O God, whose only-begotten Son, by his life, death and
        resurrection, has purchased for us the rewards of eternal
        salvation; grant, we beseech you, that meditating upon these
        mysteries in the most holy rosary of the Blessed Virgin Mary,
        we may imitate what they contain, and obtain what they
        promise. Through the same Christ our Lord. Amen.\n\n
        V/. Most Sacred Heart of Jesus\n
        R/. Have mercy on us.\n
        V/. Immaculate Heart of Mary\n
        R/. Pray for us.\n
        V/. St. Joseph\n
        R/. Pray for us.\n
        V/. St. John the Evangelist\n
        R/. Pray for us.\n
        V/. St. Louis-Marie de Montfort\n
        R/. Pray for us.\n\n
        In the name of the Father, etc
    </string>


    <string name="catena">
        Antiphon. Who is she that comes forth as the morning
        rising, fair as the moon, bright as the sun, terrible as an army
        set in battle array?\n\n

        My soul glorifies the Lord,*
        my spirit rejoices in God, my Saviour.
        He looks on his servant in her lowliness;*
        henceforth all ages will call me blessed.\n\n

        The Almighty works marvels for me.*
        Holy his name!
        His mercy is from age to age,*
        on those who fear him.\n\n

        He puts forth his arm in strength*
        and scatters the proud-hearted.
        He casts the mighty from their thrones*
        and raises the lowly.\n\n

        He fills the starving with good things,*
        sends the rich away empty.\n\n

        He protects Israel, his servant,*
        remembering his mercy,
        the mercy promised to our fathers,*
        to Abraham and his sons for ever.\n\n

        Glory be to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy
        Spirit. As it was in the beginning, is now, and ever shall be, world
        without end, Amen.\n\n

        Antiphon. Who is she that comes forth as the morning
        rising, fair as the moon, bright as the sun, terrible as an army
        set in battle array?\n\n

        V/. O Mary, conceived without sin.\n
        R/. Pray for us who have recourse to you.\n\n

        Let us pray\n\n

        O Lord Jesus Christ, our mediator with the Father, you have
        been pleased to appoint the most Blessed Virgin, your Mother,
        to be our mother also, and our mediatrix with you, mercifully
        grant that whoever comes to you seeking your favours may
        rejoice to receive all of them through her. Amen.
    </string>

    <string name="oracoes_finais">
        In the name of the Father, etc.\n\n
        We fly to your patronage, O Holy Mother of God; despise
        not our prayers in our necessities, but ever deliver us from all
        dangers, O glorious and blessed Virgin.\n\n
        V/. (Invocation appropriate to praesidium)
        R/. Pray for us.\n
        V/. Mary Immaculate, Mediatrix of all Graces\n
        R/. Pray for us.\n
        V/. St. Michael and St. Gabriel\n
        R/. Pray for us.\n
        V/. All you heavenly Powers, Mary\'s Legion
        of Angels\n
        R/. Pray for us.\n
        V/. St. John the Baptist\n
        R/. Pray for us.\n
        V/. Saints Peter and Paul\n
        R/. Pray for us\n

        Confer, O Lord, on us,
        Who serve beneath the standard of Mary,
        That fullness of faith in you and trust in her,
        To which it is given to conquer the world.
        Grant us a lively faith, animated by charity,
        Which will enable us to perform all our actions
        From the motive of pure love of you,
        And ever to see you and serve you in our neighbour;
        A faith, firm and immovable as a rock,
        Through which we shall rest tranquil and steadfast
        Amid the crosses, toils and disappointments of life;
        A courageous faith which will inspire us
        To undertake and carry out without hesitation
        Great things for your glory and for the salvation of souls;
        A faith which will be our Legion\'s Pillar of Fire —
        To lead us forth united —
        To kindle everywhere the fires of divine love—
        To enlighten those who are in darkness and in the shadow
        of death—
        To inflame those who are lukewarm—
        To bring back life to those who are dead in sin;
        And which will guide our own feet in the way of peace;
        So that — the battle of life over —
        Our Legion may reassemble,
        Without the loss of any one,
        In the kingdom of your love and glory. Amen.\n\n

        May the souls of our departed legionaries
        And the souls of all the faithful departed
        Through the mercy of God rest in peace. Amen.\n\n

        In the name of the Father, etc.
    </string>

    <string name="oracao_frank_duff">
        God our Father,\n\n
        You inspired your servant Frank Duff with a profound insight into the mystery of your Church,
        the Body of Christ, and of the place of Mary, the Mother of Jesus in this mystery.\n\n
        In his immense desire to share this insight with others, and in filial dependence on Mary,
        he formed her Legion to be a sign of her maternal love for the world, and a means of enlisting
        all her children in the Church\'s evangelizing work.\n\n
        We thank you Father, for the graces conferred on him, and for the benefits accruing to the Church from
        his courageous and shining faith.\n\n
        With confidence we beg you, that through his intercession you grant the petititon we lay before you.....\n\n
        We ask too, that if it be in accordance with your will, the holiness of his life may be acknowledged by the Church for the glory of your Name,\n\n
        through Christ Our Lord,\n\n
        Amen.
    </string>

    <string name="ordem_da_reuniao">
        1- Opening Prayers\n\n
        2- Spiritual Reading\n\n
        3- Minutes of the previous meeting \n\n
        4- Standing Instructions\n\n
        5- Welcome to new candidates and visitors and roll call\n\n
        6- Treasurer\'s Report \n\n
        7- Reports by each member\n\n
        8- Catena - Allocutio\n\n
        9- The Secret Bag is passed \n\n
        10- Continuation of the Reports on assigned works\n\n
        11- President gives teams their work assignments \n\n
        12- Handbook Study\n\n
        13- Other Business\n\n
        14- Concluding Prayers from the Tessera, and the final blessing from the Priest
    </string>

</resources>
